

Oh Soong Teng

Software Developer

Profile

I'm Oh Soong Teng, a 24-year-old graduate in software engineering from Universiti Tun Hussein Onn Malaysia (UTHM) in 2023. I've got hands-on experience in web development using Vue.js, Node.js, and MongoDB. I love coding and solving challenges.

Education

2017-2018

STPM Science Stream SMJK Yok Bin, Melaka CGPA - 3.17

2019-2023

Bachelor of Computer Science (Software Engineering) with Honours University Tun Hussein Onn Malaysia CGPA - 3.79

Contact

Phone +60 17-250 8588

Email ohst1999@hotmail.com

Website https://raw.githack.com/erazersyo/ About-Me/main/main.html

Experience

Fusionex Group

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023 Internship

Feb 2023 - Present Full Stack Software Developer

- Develop website using Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB.

- Collaborated with Business Analyst and develop the system according to their requirement.

Skills

HTML CSS Javascript (basic) Vue.js

PHP (basic) Node.js

C (basic) MySQL

Asp.net (basic) MongoDB

Languages

English Malay

Chinese Japanese (JLPT N2)